Guide to the Radio TV Reports Infomercial Collection, 1990-1996 RL.01062
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
Radio TV Reports Infomercial collection
1990-1996
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
Radio TV Reports Inc.
RL.01062
12 Linear Feet
Broadcast service company that records, transcribes and monitors radio and television programming. Collection spans the years 1990-1996 and consists of over 800 as-broadcast televised infomercials and public service programs recorded on VHS. Topics include direct marketing for health and beauty aids, kitchen appliances, exercise equipment, wealth management and collectible items. Celebrities featured as spokespersons include Cher, Joe Theisman, Richard Simmons and Victoria Jackson. Services represented include health and insurance providers and nonprofit organizations such as the New Jersey Education Association. Acquired as part of the John W. Hartman Center for Sales, Advertising & Marketing History.
149 Items
Access Restrictions
Collection is open for research.
Researchers must register and agree to copyright and privacy laws before using this collection.
In addition, original audiovisual materials are closed to patron use. Research Services staff need to produce use copies before contents can be accessed.
All or portions of this collection may be housed off-site in Duke University's Library Service Center. The library may require up to 48 hours to retrieve these materials for research use.
Please contact Research Services staff before visiting the David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library to use this collection.
Provenance
The Radio TV Reports Infomercial Collection were received by the David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library as a gift in 2012.
Collection Overview
Collection spans the years 1990-1996 and consists of over 800 as-broadcast televised infomercials and public service programs recorded on VHS. Topics include direct marketing for health and beauty aids, kitchen appliances, exercise equipment, wealth management and collectible items. Celebrities featured as spokespersons include Cher, Joe Theisman, Richard Simmons and Victoria Jackson. Services represented include health and insurance providers and nonprofit organizations such as the New Jersey Education Association.
Collection Arrangement
VHS tapes have been numbered. Collection arranged numerically. Gaps in the numbering represent tapes not received with the collection.
Related Material
Related material may also be found in the following Hartman Center collections:
Adrienne Cohen Papers
John Stevenson Papers
Lester Wunderman Papers
Wunderman Archives
Direct marketing; Infomercials; Advertising, Public service; Television advertising; Videotapes; New Jersey Education Association; John W. Hartman Center for Sales, Advertising & Marketing History; Jackson, Victoria; Cher, 1946-; Theisman, Joe; Radio TV Reports Inc.; Simmons, Richard
- Original Tapes, 1990-1996; 1
  - Tape 1 - Mega Memory Photographic Memory, FNN-TV, 1990 May 31, 3:00 AM; $50,000 Opportunity Showcase--Entrepreneurs, FNN-TV, 1990 May 31 3:30 AM; Howard Ruff--Achieve Prosperity in the 90s, FNN-TV, 1990 May 31 4:00 AM; Fran Tarkenton--Personal Achievement, FNN-TV, 1990 May 31 4:30 AM., 1990-05-31; 1
    - Original VHS videocassette (Box 1, Video-cassette Tape 1)
  - Tape 2 - Arnold's Gourmet Kitchen--Kitchenmate, WWOR-TV, 1990 June 2, 6:00 AM; Incredible Breakthrough--Liquid Lustre, WWOR-TV, 1990 June 2, 6:30 AM; Unlocking the Mystery of Marriage, WWOR-TV, 1990 June 2, 7:00 AM; Victoria Jackson--Beauty Breakthrough for the 90s, WWOR-TV, 1990 June 2, 7:30 AM., 1990-06-02; 2
    - Original VHS videocassette (Box 1, Video-cassette Tape 2)
  - Tape 3 - Soloflex, WNBC-TV, 1990 June 2, 1:00 PM., 1990-06-02; 3
    - Original VHS videocassette (Box 1, Video-cassette Tape 3)
  - Tape 4 - Richard Simmons--Deal a Meal, WWOR-TV1990 June2, 8:00 AM; Harvey's Smart Kitchen--Electric Kitchen, WWOR-TV1990 June2, 8:30 AM; Vikki Lamotia--You Can Look Younger, WWOR-TV1990 June2, 9:00 AM; Making Life Easier with Dave Clark--Clark Snackmaster, WWOR-TV1990 June2, 9:30 AM., 1990-06-02; 4
    - Original VHS videocassette (Box 1, Video-cassette Tape 4)
  - Tape 5 - Amazing Discoveries--Astonish Cleaner, WNYW-TV, 1990 June 3, 10:00 AM; Arnold's Gourmet Kitchen--Daily Maintenance, WNYW-TV, 1990 June3, 10:30 AM., 1990-06-03; 5
    - Original VHS videocassette (Box 1, Video-cassette Tape 5)
  - Tape 6 - Joe Theisman 30 Minute Workout, WWOR-TV, 1990 June 3, 12:00 AM., 1990-06-03; 6
    - Original VHS videocassette (Box 1, Video-cassette Tape 6)
  - Tape 7 - Financial Freedom, LIF-TV, 1990 June 5, 3:00 AM., 1990-06-05; 7
    - Original VHS videocassette (Box 1, Video-cassette Tape 7)
  - Tape 8 - Richard Simmons--Deal a Meal, Lifetime, 1990 Mar 21, 5:30 AM; Gary Kakson--How to Get a Second Paycheck, Lifetime, 1990 Mar 21, 6:00 AM; Victoria Jackson--Beauty Breakthrough for the 90s, Lifetime, 1990 Mar 21, 6:30 AM., 1990-03-21; 8
    - Original VHS videocassette (Box 1, Video-cassette Tape 8)
  - Tape 9 - Victoria Jackson--Beauty Breakthrough for the 90s, Lifetime, 1990 Mar 22, 1:00 AM; Amazing Discovery--Natural White, Lifetime, 1990 Mar 22, 1:30 AM; Arnold's Gourmet Kitchen--Kitchenmate, Lifetime, 1990 Mar 22, 2:00 AM; Susan Purcell--Cash for the Asking, Lifetime, 1990 Mar 22, 2:30 AM., 1990-03-22; 9
    - Original VHS videocassette (Box 1, Video-cassette Tape 9)
  - Tape 10 - Cashing in on the Cashless Society, LIF-TV, 1990 June 5, 1:30 AM; Solid Gold Rock and Roll, LIF-TV, 1990 June 5, 2:00 AM; Susan Purcell--Cash for the Asking, LIF-TV, 1990 June 5, 2:30 AM., 1990-06-05; 10
    - Original VHS videocassette (Box 1, Video-cassette Tape 10)
  - Tape 11 - Arnold's Gourmet Kitchen--Great Wok of China, Family Channel, 1990 June 6, 3:00 AM; Joe McKenzie Breakthroughs--Hobei Kitchen Utensil, Family Channel, 1990 June 6, 3:30 AM; Kevin Trudeau--Memory Mega, Family Channel, 1990 June 6, 4:00 AM; Amazing Discovery--Astonish Cleaner, Family Channel, 1990 June 6, 4:30 AM., 1990-06-06; 11
    - Original VHS videocassette (Box 1, Video-cassette Tape 11)
  - Tape 12 - Michael Reed--Subliminal Communications, USA1990 June 8, 6:00 AM; Soloflex (female) Male-Dance, USA1990 June 8, 6:30 AM., 1990-06-08; 12
    - Original VHS videocassette (Box 1, Video-cassette Tape 12)
  - Tape 13 - Arnold's Gourmet Kitchen--Great Wok of China, WNYW-TV, 1990 June 3, 9:00 AM; Amazing Discovery--Natural White, WNYW-TV, 1990 June 3, 9:30 AM., 1990-06-03; 13
    - Original VHS videocassette (Box 1, Video-cassette Tape 13)
  - Tape 14 - Better Ways to Better Grades (Where There Is a Will There Is an A), TBS, 1990 June 3, 12:00 AM; Unlocking the Mystery of Marriage, TBS, 1990 June 3, 12:30 AM; Is There Love After Marriage--Dave Clark, TBS, 1990 June 3, 1:00 AM; Victoria Jackson--Beauty Breakthrough for the 90s, TBS, 1990 June 3, 1:30 AM., 1990-06-03; 14
    - Original VHS videocassette (Box 1, Video-cassette Tape 14)
  - Tape 15 - JS&A, The Making of a Commercial--Blocker Sunglasses, WPIX-TV, 1990 June 9, 7:30 AM., 1990-06-09; 15
    - Original VHS videocassette (Box 1, Video-cassette Tape 15)
  - Tape 16 - Kitchen Mate, WNYW-TV, 1990 June 9, 6:00 AM; Stain-A-Rator, WNYW-TV, 1990 June 9, 6:30 AM; The World Tomorrow, WNYW-TV, 1990 June 9, 7:00 AM; Auri--John Ritter, WNYW-TV, 1990 June 9, 7:30 AM., 1990-06-09; 16
    - Original VHS videocassette (Box 1, Video-cassette Tape 16)
  - Tape 17 - Craftmatic Bed--Better Sleep, WWOR-TV, 1990 June 9, 12:30 AM., 1990-06-09; 17
    - Original VHS videocassette (Box 1, Video-cassette Tape 17)
  - Tape 18 - Better Ways to Better Grades (Where There Is a Will There Is an A)--John Ritter, WWOR-TV, 1990 June 9, 7:30 AM., 1990-06-09; 18
    - Original VHS videocassette (Box 1, Video-cassette Tape 18)
  - Tape 19 - Regina Housekeeper Plus, WVTV-TV, 1990 June 10, 10:00 AM., 1990-06-10; 19
    - Original VHS videocassette (Box 1, Video-cassette Tape 19)
  - Tape 20 - Stain-A-Rator, WWOR-TV, 1990 June 9, 9:30 AM., 1990-06-09; 20
    - Original VHS videocassette (Box 1, Video-cassette Tape 20)
  - Tape 21 - Lifesigns Stop Smoking featuring E,L, Marshall, Florence Henderson, WNYW-TV, 1990 June 16, 7:00 AM., 1990-06-16; 21
    - Original VHS videocassette (Box 1, Video-cassette Tape 21)
  - Tape 22 - Command Performance Relationship between You and Your Dog--Bruce Weitz, WPGH-TV, 1990 June 16, 9:30 AM., 1990-06-16; 22
    - Original VHS videocassette (Box 1, Video-cassette Tape 22)
  - Tape 23 - Now You're Cooking--Super Server featuring Christopher Hewett, WWOR-TV, 1990 June 16, 8:30 AM., 1990-06-16; 23
    - Original VHS videocassette (Box 1, Video-cassette Tape 23)
  - Tape 24 - Nike, TBS, 1990 June 17, 11:30 AM., 1990-06-17; 24
    - Original VHS videocassette (Box 1, Video-cassette Tape 24)
  - Tape 25 - Nike, TBS, 1990 June 17, 12:00 AM., 1990-06-17; 25
    - Original VHS videocassette (Box 1, Video-cassette Tape 25)
  - Tape 26 - Hair Club for Men featuring Sy Sperling, WWOR-TV, 1990 June 16, 10:30 AM., 1990-06-16; 26
    - Original VHS videocassette (Box 1, Video-cassette Tape 26)
  - Tape 27 - Amazing Discovery--Natural White, Family Channel, 1990 Sep 28, 3:30 AM; Flowbee Vacuum Haircut, Family Channel, 1990 Sep 28, 4:00 AM; Being Your Own Boss, Family Channel, 1990 Sep 28, 4:30 AM; Amazing Micro Diet--Kathy Lee Crosby, Family Channel, 1990 Sep 28, 5:00 AM., 1990-09-28; 27
    - Original VHS videocassette (Box 1, Video-cassette Tape 27)
  - Tape 28 - Cuisine International Presents The Great Wall of China, WWOR-TV, 1990 June 24, 12:00 AM., 1990-06-24; 28
    - Original VHS videocassette (Box 1, Video-cassette Tape 28)
  - Tape 29 - Victoria Jackson--Beauty Breakthrough for the 90s, WWOR-TV, 1990 Sep 22, 8:00 AM; Inside Secrets--Magic White, WWOR-TV, 1990 Sep 22, 8:30 AM; Personal Power--Anthony Robbins, WWOR-TV, 1990 Sep 22, 9:00 AM; Entrepreneur--Be Your Own Boss, WWOR-TV, 1990 Sep 22, 9:30 AM., 1990-09-22; 29
    - Original VHS videocassette (Box 1, Video-cassette Tape 29)
  - Tape 30 - Amazing Micro Diet--Kathy Lee Crosby, WWOR-TV, 1991 Jan 5, 8:00 AM; Incredible Breakthrough--Sisan Iron, WWOR-TV, 1991 Jan 5, 8:30 AM; Kathy Smith Diet--Fat Burning System, WWOR-TV, 1991 Jan 5, 9:00 AM; Arnold's Gourmet Kitchen--Kitchenmate, WWOR-TV, 1991 Jan 5, 9:30 AM., 1991-01-05; 30
    - Original VHS videocassette (Box 1, Video-cassette Tape 30)
  - Tape 31 - This is the NFL, NBC-TV,1991 Jan 13, 12:00 PM; Where There Is a Will There Is an A--John Ritter, NBC-TV,1991 Jan 13, 12:30 PM; Victoria Jackson--Beauty Breakthrough for the 90s, NBC-TV,1991 Jan 13, 1:00 PM; Sisan Steam Iron--Incredible Breakthrough featuring Linda Michaels, NBC-TV,1991 Jan 13, 1:30 PM., 1991-01-13; 31
    - Original VHS videocassette (Box 2, Video-cassette Tape 31)
  - Tape 32 - Beauty Breakthroughs--Amazing Micro Diet, WWOR-TV, 1991 Jan 1, 10:00 AM; Health Innovations--When You're Ready to Quit, WWOR-TV, 1991 Jan 1, 10:30 AM; Sulit-T-Go Age-Free Skin, WWOR-TV, 1991 Jan 1, 11:00 AM; Inside Secrets--Magic White featuring Richard Bey, WWOR-TV, 1991 Jan 1, 11:30 AM., 1991-01-01; 32
    - Original VHS videocassette (Box 2, Video-cassette Tape 32)
  - Tape 35 - Hair Club for Men featuring Sy Sperling, WNBC-TV, 1991 Jan 13, 12:17 AM; Brain Supercharger--Millionaire's Mind, WNBC-TV, 1991 Jan 13, 12:47 AM., 1991-01-13; 33
    - Original VHS videocassette (Box 2, Video-cassette Tape 35)
  - Tape 36 - The Love Phone--Jessica Hahn, WWOR-TV, 1991 Jan 5, 12:30 AM; When You're Ready to Quit Smoking, WWOR-TV, 1991 Jan 5, 1:00 AM; The Weight Loss Revolution--Kathy Lee Crosby, WWOR-TV, 1991 Jan 5, 1:30 AM., 1991-01-05; 34
    - Original VHS videocassette (Box 2, Video-cassette Tape 36)
  - Tape 37 - Arnold's Gourmet Kitchen--Kitchenmate, WNYW-TV, 1991Jan 6, 8:30 AM; Weight Loss Revolution--Amazing Micro Diet, WNYW-TV, 1991Jan 6, 9:00 AM; Anushka--Erin Gray Straight Talk, WNYW-TV, 1991Jan 6, 9:30 AM., 1991-01-06; 35
    - Original VHS videocassette (Box 2, Video-cassette Tape 37)
  - Tape 38 - Incredible Breakthrough--The Punch Connection (Craft for the Family), WPIX-TV, 1991 Jan 21, 7:00 AM; St, Go Skin Care System, WPIX-TV, 1991 Jan 21, 7:30 AM., 1991-01-21; 36
    - Original VHS videocassette (Box 2, Video-cassette Tape 38)
  - Tape 39 - Now You're Cooking--Super Snacker, WWOR-TV, 1991 Jan 6, 12:30 AM; Diet Disc Program--HerbaLife, WWOR-TV, 1991 Jan 6, 1:00 AM; Financial Freedom with John Davidson, WWOR-TV, 1991 Jan 6, 1:30 AM., 1991-01-06; 37
    - Original VHS videocassette (Box 2, Video-cassette Tape 39)
  - Tape 40 - Sisan Steam Iron--Incredible Breakthrough, WWOR-TV, 1991 Jan 12, 8:00 AM; Neutra Plak--Instant White, WWOR-TV, 1991 Jan 12, 8:30 AM., 1991-01-12; 38
    - Original VHS videocassette (Box 2, Video-cassette Tape 40)
  - Tape 41 - The Miracle Blade, WWOR-TV, 1991 Jan 5, 6:00 AM; The Weight Loss Revolution--Kathy Lee Crosby, WWOR-TV, 1991 Jan 5, 6:30 AM; The Power Play--Richard Ames, WWOR-TV, 1991 Jan 5, 7:00 AM; Health Innovations--When You're Ready to Quit, WWOR-TV, 1991 Jan 5, 7:30 AM., 1991-01-05; 39
    - Original VHS videocassette (Box 2, Video-cassette Tape 41)
  - Tape 42 - Snak Master--Making Life Easier, WNYW-TV, 1991Jan 19, 8:30 AM; Fat Burning System--Kathy Smith, WNYW-TV, 1991Jan 19, 9:00 AM; Incredible Breakthrough--Sisan Iron, WNYW-TV, 1991Jan 19, 9:30 AM., 1991-01-19; 40
    - Original VHS videocassette (Box 2, Video-cassette Tape 42)
  - Tape 43 - Weight Loss Revolution--Amazing Micro Diet, WWOR-TV, 1991 Jan 19, 8:00 AM; Sisan Iron--Incredible Breakthrough, WWOR-TV, 1991 Jan 19, 8:30 AM; Fit One 20-Minute Workout, WWOR-TV, 1991 Jan 19, 9:00 AM; Arnold's Gourmet Kitchen--Kitchenmate, WWOR-TV, 1991 Jan 19, 9:30 AM., 1991-01-19; 41
    - Original VHS videocassette (Box 2, Video-cassette Tape 43)
  - Tape 44 - Jet Steam Oven--American Harvest, KTMA-TV Minneapolis, 1991 Jan 13, 3:30 PM., 1991-01-13; 42
    - Original VHS videocassette (Box 2, Video-cassette Tape 44)
  - Tape 45 - Incredible Breakthrough--Turro Iron, WWOR-TV, 1991 Jan 26, 10:00 AM; Amazing Micro Diet--Kathy Lee Crosby, WWOR-TV, 1991 Jan 26, 10:30 AM., 1991-01-26; 43
    - Original VHS videocassette (Box 2, Video-cassette Tape 45)
  - Tape 46 - The Good Life--Getting Yours, WNYW-TV, 1991 Jan 27, 10:00 AM; Blu Blockers Sunglasses, WNYW-TV, 1991 Jan 27, 10:30 AM., 1991-01-27; 44
    - Original VHS videocassette (Box 2, Video-cassette Tape 46)
  - Tape 47 - How to Make 1,000 a Day--The Trustee Game, WPIX-TV, 1991 Jan 26, 7:00 AM; How to Get a Second Paycheck--Hawaiian Style, WPIX-TV, 1991 Jan 26, 7:30 AM., 1991-01-26; 45
    - Original VHS videocassette (Box 2, Video-cassette Tape 47)
  - Tape 48 - Sisan Iron--Synchronal, WNYW-TV, 1991 Jan 27, 8:30 AM; Anushka--Erin Gray Straight Talk, WNYW-TV, 1991 Jan 27, 9:00 AM; Soloflex--Family Kid Soccer, WNYW-TV, 1991 Jan 27, 9:30 AM., 1991-01-27; 46
    - Original VHS videocassette (Box 2, Video-cassette Tape 48)
  - Tape 49 - Fat Burning System--Kathy Smith, WNYW-TV, 1991 Feb 3, 10:00 AM; Retinoid Regimen II--War Against Wrinkles with Juliet Prowse, WNYW-TV, 1991 Feb 3, 10:30 AM., 1991-02-03; 47
    - Original VHS videocassette (Box 2, Video-cassette Tape 49)
  - Tape 50 - Hair Club for Men, WNBC-TV, 1991 Feb 3, 12:00 PM; Deal a Meal USA, WNBC-TV, 1991 Feb 3, 12:30 PM., 1991-02-03; 48
    - Original VHS videocassette (Box 2, Video-cassette Tape 50)
  - Tape 51 - You Can Look Younger--Vickki LaMotta and Lee Meriwether, WWOR-TV, Undated, 8:00 AM; Personal Power--Michael O'Brien, WWOR-TV, Undated, 8:30 AM., 49
    - Original VHS videocassette (Box 2, Video-cassette Tape 51)
  - Tape 52 - Tom Vu--Secrets of Success (1-hour), NBC-TV,1991 Feb 17, 12:00 PM., 1991-02-17; 50
    - Original VHS videocassette (Box 2, Video-cassette Tape 52)
  - Tape 53 - Magic White--Richard Bey, WWOR-TV, 1991 Feb 17, 12:00 PM; Turbo Iron, WWOR-TV, 1991 Feb 17, 12:30 PM; HerbaLife, WWOR-TV, 1991 Feb 17, 1:00 PM., 1991-02-17; 51
    - Original VHS videocassette (Box 2, Video-cassette Tape 53)
  - Tape 54 - Blu Blockers Sunglasses, WPIX-TV, 1991 Feb 23, 7:00 AM; Human Calculator--Scott Plansford, WPIX-TV, 1991 Feb 23, 7:30 AM., 1991-02-23; 52
    - Original VHS videocassette (Box 2, Video-cassette Tape 54)
  - Tape 55 - Sisan Iron, WPIX-TV, 1991 Feb 23, 8:00 AM; Neutra Plak--Instant White--Judi Barton, WPIX-TV, 1991 Feb 23, 8:30 AM., 1991-02-23; 53
    - Original VHS videocassette (Box 2, Video-cassette Tape 55)
  - Tape 56 - Rock and Roll Era--Time Life Music, WPIX-TV, 1991 Mar 2, 7:00 AM; Human Calculator--Scott Plansford, WPIX-TV, 1991 Mar 2, 7:30 AM., 1991-03-02; 54
    - Original VHS videocassette (Box 2, Video-cassette Tape 56)
  - Tape 57 - Fit One Fitness Quest, WNYW-TV, 1991 Mar 3, 9:00 AM; A Second Paycheck, WNYW-TV, 1991 Mar 3, 9:30 AM; War Against Wrinkles, WNYW-TV, 1991 Mar 3, 10:00 AM., 1991-03-03; 55
    - Original VHS videocassette (Box 2, Video-cassette Tape 57)
  - Tape 58 - Blu Blockers Sunglasses, WPIX-TV, 1991 Mar 9, 7:00 AM; Take 30 30-Minute Workout with Joe Theisman, S, Easton, Dave Scott, WPIX-TV, 1991 Mar 9, 7:30 AM; Deal a Meal USA, WPIX-TV, 1991 Mar 9, 8:00 AM; Where There Is a Will There Is an A--John Ritter, WPIX-TV, 1991 Mar 9, 8:30 AM., 1991-03-09; 56
    - Original VHS videocassette (Box 2, Video-cassette Tape 58)
  - Tape 59 - Fitness Quest--Abdominizer, WWOR-TV, 1991 Mar 23, 6:00 AM; Power Bands--Joe Namath, WWOR-TV, 1991 Mar 23, 6:30 AM; Models Choice Collection--S-T-Go, WWOR-TV, 1991 Mar 23, 7:00 AM., 1991-03-23; 57
    - Original VHS videocassette (Box 2, Video-cassette Tape 59)
  - Tape 60 - Brain Supercharger--Millionaire's Mind, WNBC-TV, 1991 Mar 30, 6:30 AM; Will Your Kid Make the Grade--Michael Landon, WNBC-TV, 1991 Mar 30, 7:00 AM., 1991-03-30; 58
    - Original VHS videocassette (Box 2, Video-cassette Tape 60)
  - Tape 61 - Merve Wrinkle Cream--The All America Miracle Search, WWOR-TV, 1991 Apr 12, 12:00 AM., 1991-04-12; 59
    - Original VHS videocassette (Box 2, Video-cassette Tape 61)
  - Tape 62 - Freedom from Pain--Therapy Plus, WPIX-TV, 1991 Apr 27, 7:30 AM; Human Calculator--Scott Plansford, WPIX-TV, 1991 Apr 27, 8:00 AM., 1991-04-27; 60
    - Original VHS videocassette (Box 2, Video-cassette Tape 62)
  - Tape 63 - The Early 90s Dog Training--Bruce Weitz, Family Channel, 1991 May 9, 2:00 AM; The Power Steamer--Mike Levi, Family Channel, 1991 May 9, 2:30 AM; Soloflex--Football Tennis, Family Channel, 1991 May 9, 3:00 AM; Molecular Medicine--Vitamin Diet MDR Fitness, Family Channel, 1991 May 9, 3:30 AM., 1991-05-09; 61
    - Original VHS videocassette (Box 3, Video-cassette Tape 63)
  - Tape 64 - Deal a Meal--Sweating to the Oldies, WWOR-TV, 1991 May 11, 10:00 AM; The Juiceman--Richard Bey, WWOR-TV, 1991 May 11, 10:30 AM., 1991-05-11; 62
    - Original VHS videocassette (Box 3, Video-cassette Tape 64)
  - Tape 65 - Fantasy for Sale--World Tomorrow, WPIX-TV, 1991 July 13, 6:00 AM; The Millionaire School, WPIX-TV, 1991 July 13, 6:30 AM., 1991-07-13; 63
    - Original VHS videocassette (Box 3, Video-cassette Tape 65)
  - Tape 67 - Deal a Meal--Richard Simmons, WWOR-TV, 1991 July 13, 8:00 AM; Celeste Caruso Hairsetter--Anna Stuart, WWOR-TV, 1991 July 13, 8:30 AM; The Greatest Animated Bible Stories, WWOR-TV, 1991 July 13, 9:00 AM., 1991-07-13; 64
    - Original VHS videocassette (Box 3, Video-cassette Tape 67)
  - Tape 68 - Deal a Meal--Sweating to the Oldies, WWOR-TV, 1991 July 20, 10:00 AM; Victoria Jackson--Beauty Breakthrough for the 90s with Meredith Baxter-Bernie, Ali McGraw, WWOR-TV, 1991 July 20, 10:30 AM., 1991-07-20; 65
    - Original VHS videocassette (Box 3, Video-cassette Tape 68)
  - Tape 69 - Celeste Caruso Hairsetter--Anna Stuart, WWOR-TV, 1991 July 20, 8:30 AM; War Against Wrinkles, WWOR-TV, 1991 July 20, 9:00 AM., 1991-07-20; 66
    - Original VHS videocassette (Box 3, Video-cassette Tape 69)
  - Tape 70 - Game of Love--Jessica Hahn, WWOR-TV, 1991 June 8, 12:30 AM; Will Your Kid Make the Grade--Michael Landon, WWOR-TV, 1991 June 8, 1:00 AM; Personal Power--Anthony Robbins, WWOR-TV, 1991 June 8, 1:30 AM., 1991-06-08; 67
    - Original VHS videocassette (Box 3, Video-cassette Tape 70)
  - Tape 71 - Beauty Breakthrough II--Victoria Jackson, WWOR-TV, 1991 Aug 17, 8:00 AM; Wealth Without Risk--Charles Givens, WWOR-TV, 1991 Aug 17, 8:30 AM; Family Entertainment--The Miracle of Jesus, WWOR-TV, 1991 Aug 17, 9:00 AM; This is Club Med--Paradise Found, WWOR-TV, 1991 Aug 17, 9:30 AM., 1991-08-17; 68
    - Original VHS videocassette (Box 3, Video-cassette Tape 71)
  - Tape 72 - Deal a Meal--Sweating to the Oldies, WWOR-TV, 1991 July 27, 8:00 AM; Personal Power--Robert Bey, Fran Tarkenton, WWOR-TV, 1991 July 27, 8:30 AM; Family Entertainment--Bible, WWOR-TV, 1991 July 27, 9:00 AM; Freedom from Pain--Therapy Plus, WWOR-TV, 1991 July 27, 9:30 AM., 1991-07-27; 69
    - Original VHS videocassette (Box 3, Video-cassette Tape 72)
  - Tape 73 - Blu Blockers Sunglasses--Rapper, WPIX-TV, 1991 Aug 3, 8:00 AM., 1991-08-03; 70
    - Original VHS videocassette (Box 3, Video-cassette Tape 73)
  - Tape 74 - Say Goodbye to Wrinkles--Vickki LaMotta, Lyle Wagganer, WWOR-TV, 1991 Sep 21, 9:00 AM; Fit One Fitness Quest, WWOR-TV, 1991 Sep 21, 9:30 AM., 1991-09-21; 71
    - Original VHS videocassette (Box 3, Video-cassette Tape 74)
  - Tape 75 - Hooked on Phonics--Chad Murdock, WPIX-TV, 1991 Sep 21, 6:30 AM; How to Be a Millionaire--The Millionaire School with Dave Del Dotto, WPIX-TV, 1991 Sep 21, 7:30 AM., 1991-09-21; 72
    - Original VHS videocassette (Box 3, Video-cassette Tape 75)
  - Tape 76 - Principal Secrets--Victoria Principal, WWOR-TV, 1991 Aug 24, 7:30 AM., 1991-08-24; 73
    - Original VHS videocassette (Box 3, Video-cassette Tape 76)
  - Tape 77 - Volvo Cars San Diego, KLSI-TV, 1991 Sep 29, 1:00 AM., 1991-09-29; 74
    - Original VHS videocassette (Box 3, Video-cassette Tape 77)
  - Tape 78 - Fit One Fitness Quest, WWOR-TV, 1991 Sep 7, 6:00 AM; When You're Ready to Quit Smoking, WWOR-TV, 1991 Sep 7, 7:30 AM., 1991-09-07; 75
    - Original VHS videocassette (Box 3, Video-cassette Tape 78)
  - Tape 79 - Secrets of the Rich and Successful--Jay McCorkle, WNYW-TV, 1991 Sep 14, 4:30 PM., 1991-09-14; 76
    - Original VHS videocassette (Box 3, Video-cassette Tape 79)
  - Tape 80 - Healing a Broken Planet, WPIX-TV, 1991 Oct 5, 6:00 AM; Hooked on Phonics--Chad Murdock, WPIX-TV, 1991 Oct 5, 6:30 AM; Lazervision Pinhole Glasses, WPIX-TV, 1991 Oct 5, 7:00 AM., 1991-10-05; 77
    - Original VHS videocassette (Box 3, Video-cassette Tape 80)
  - Tape 81 - Hooked on Phonics--Chad Murdock, WPIX-TV, 1991 Nov 2, 6:30 AM; Your Love in Action--Jame Robeson Ministries with Glen Campbell, WPIX-TV, 1991 Nov 2, 7:00 AM; Sani Safe Cutlery--Dexter Russell, WPIX-TV, 1991 Nov 2, 7:30 AM., 1991-11-02; 78
    - Original VHS videocassette (Box 3, Video-cassette Tape 81)
  - Tape 82 - Miracle Blade--Wayne Harvey, WNBC-TV, 1991 Oct 12, 7:00 AM., 1991-10-12; 79
    - Original VHS videocassette (Box 3, Video-cassette Tape 82)
  - Tape 83 - Victoria Jackson--Beauty Breakthrough for the 90s with Meredith Baxter-Bernie, WWOR-TV, 1991 Oct 19, 8:00 AM; Shealy Relaxmate Glasses--Dick Van Patten, WWOR-TV, 1991 Oct 19, 8:30 AM; Freedom from Pain--Therapy Plus, WWOR-TV, 1991 Oct 19, 9:00 AM; Fit One--Trailer, Bus, Skiing, WWOR-TV, 1991 Oct 19, 9:30 AM., 1991-10-19; 80
    - Original VHS videocassette (Box 3, Video-cassette Tape 83)
  - Tape 84 - Relationships Today--Dick Clark, WWOR-TV, 1991 Oct 19, 6:30 AM; The Juiceman--Richard Bey, WWOR-TV, 1991 Oct 19, 7:00 AM; Make-Over Magic--Michael Marone, WWOR-TV, 1991 Oct 19, 7:30 AM., 1991-10-19; 81
    - Original VHS videocassette (Box 3, Video-cassette Tape 84)